Luis Alberto Ceren

Software Developer

luiscerenc18@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/luis-alberto-ceren-4536531b0 Medellín, Colombia I +57 314 510 3005 I https://github.com/lcerenc661

Software developer with experience in product design and project management. 1+ work experience on the development of frontend and backend solutions, integrating cloud services with CI/CD practices. I am characterized by a proactive mindset and a commitment to continuous improvement, which drives me to constantly study and learn new technologies and concepts.

Professional Experience

FullStack Developer - Aim Edge Apps

April 2024 - Present

- Develop and mantain of web and mobile applications for our clients using technologies such as React, Next.js, Nest.js, Express.js, Flutter, AWS services, and MySQL.
- Participate in the estimation and design of new projects, defining architectures, infrastructure, and workflows.
- I have promoted practices to standardize the code in our repositories, based on a clean architecture pattern, and have proposed new code quality standards, such as HTTP response standardization, implementation of error handling strategies, and the use of Swagger with Nest to document APIs, among others.
- Conduct to research on new technologies and create proof of concepts to evaluate their potential for integration into ongoing projects.

Bilingual Analyst - Nation Wide Legal

October 2023 - April 2024

 Generated subpoenas for law firms located in California (USA), understanding the different requirements and legislation for serving them.

Product Development Engineer - AKT Motos

February 2021 - December 2022

- Coordinated the design, development, and production of plastic sub-products through direct interaction with suppliers and the assembly line.
- Designed graphic pieces for motorcycles and other needs of the area.

Skills

Technical

Python TypeScript
JavaScript Dart (Flutter)
AWS SQL React Nest
Next.js Linux Docker

Languages

Spanish: NativeEnglish: Fluent (C1)

Education

Software Developer - *Bootcamps / Courses*January 2022 - Present

Specialization in Project Management - *EAFIT*

Graduation date: December 2021

Product Design Engineering - *EAFIT*

Graduation date: June 2020

References

Mauricio Guzmán

Global Innovation Manager - LLYC

Mobile: +57 321 8823 946

Juan Camilo Echeverrí

Full Stack Developer - Wompi Mobile: +57 316 2469 782

Alejandro Ceren

Data Quality Lead - Accenture Mobile: +57 313 6031 487